Although light com let's
go I
'm not sure if this will work in the afternoon
but let's try it
because we don't have much extra time let's
try it
winnie mediterránea have when meditating in
the afternoon efe
preliminaries in the morning if you
did the preliminaries in the morning and
in cayes kurt streit a nature
you can now directly enter your
breathing are the esplanade long time
and there will be let's spend some time
focused on breathing
monjack are long installations
roxana sounds the
same there are no euros
focus on the outside sounds like
the air conditioning and the small
sounds inside this room
of travel
compare that to your heartbeat and
talk to it
abandon your focus on the air
conditioning
/ down entity
pierce and enter to center your mind
penetrating inside the heartbeat
you are the
heart you become the
heart in the film they sell sometimes it
feels delicious appetizer there is a
lot of peace triples com
very joyful paris they take several 33 see and
water
your body is
electrified mind awake and
conscious and in a perfect posture
external heartbeat  The hard way time,
parade,
stay in the heart, become the
heart, be the heart, but with that
joyful feeling,
have the joy,
imagine the ex-lover of women,
imagine that someone put
headphones on you,
on the track, Mr. Felix, and also
put headphones on your feelings
in excess, avoid the feeling stop,
and all feelings stop, in
the main, they
put plugs in your ears,
plugs in your feelings, and winter, and
inside your mind, entity, the
deeper in the heart and the
feelings, the less hard it is, place
where there's known motion, enter a
place, a space in the heart where there are
no more emotions,
Steiger Farfán is free for five
minutes, and Peter Watson is strong, keep
your state of alertness and attention very
strong / the mind back, you must have and
keep your vigilant active and ready
to bring your mind back if it is
distracted by another object and to bring it back
to the center of the heart, to the place without
feeling,
connection 3,
the exhalation in long breaths,
girl who cannot open her eyes